Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXI. ORGANIZATION
  - Sub-Series 230-552. Organization
    - Alabama State Dock Commission Terminal Railway (Alabama State Docks, Mobile, Alabama), 1948-1950 (Box 114, Folder 33)
    - Alabama State Dock Commission Terminal Railway, Alabama State Docks, Mobile, Alabama, 1937-1938 (Box 114, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 230-553. Organization
    - West Michigan Dock & Market Corporation, 1937 (Box 114, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 230-554. Organization
    - Cooper Range Railroad, 1937-1952 (Box 114, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 230-555. Organization
    - Des Moines & Central Iowa Railroad, 1937-1942 (Box 114, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 230-556. Organization
    - Railroad Restaurant Employees, 1927 (Box 114, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 230-557. Organization
    - Santa Fe Reading Room Employees, 1924 (Box 114, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 230-558. Organization
    - New Jersey, 1926-1943 (Box 114, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 230-559. Organization
    - Freight Tariff Bureau Employees-Richmond, Virginia, 1925-1926 (Box 114, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 230-560. Organization
    - Oil Pipe Line Employees, 1926 (Box 114, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 230-561. Organization
    - Bureau Employees-Meridian, Mississippi, 1922 (Box 114, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 230-562. Organization
    - Twin Cities of Minnesota, 1921-1936 (Box 114, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 230-563. Organization
    - Mississippi Warrior Service, Federal Barge Lines, 1933 (Box 114, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 230-564. Organization
    - Merchants Carloading Company-Newark, New Jersey, 1947 (Box 114, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 230-565. Organization
    - Northeast Oklahoma Railroad, 1928-1951 (Box 114, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 230-566. Organization
    - Toledo and Western Railroad, 1928 (Box 114, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 230-567. Organization
    - Newburgh & South Shore Railway Company, 1941-1952 (Box 114, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 230-568. Organization
    - Fairport, Painesville & Eastern Railroad, 1941-1942 (Box 114, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 230-569. Organization
    - Montpelier & Wells River Railroad, 1942 (Box 114, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 230-570. Organization
    - South San Francisco Union Stock Yards Company, 1942 (Box 114, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 230-572. Organization
    - Maryland & Pennsylvania, 1942-1954 (Box 114, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 230-573. Organization
    - Monessen-Southwestern Railroad Company, 1942 (Box 114, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 230-574. Organization
    - Smoky Mountain Railway, 1942-1947 (Box 114, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 230-575. Organization
    - Atlantic & Yadkin Railway Company, 1943 (Box 114, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 230-576. Organization
    - Illinois Northern Railway, 1935-1949 (Box 114, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 230-577. Organization
    - Cincinnati and Lake Erie Railway (C. & L. E.), 1936-1937 (Box 114, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 230-578. Organization
    - Great Lakes Transit Corporation, 1933 (Box 114, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 230-579. Organization
    - Tri-Cities, 1937 (Box 114, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 230-580. Organization
    - Florida, 1926 (Box 114, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 230-581. Organization
    - Republic of Honduras, 1926 (Box 114, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 230-582. Organization
    - Georgia, 1924 (Box 114, Folder 63)
      Oct. 22, 1924.
  - Sub-Series 230-583. Organization
    - Mississippi, 1925 (Box 114, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 230-584. Organization
    - Slogan Rubber Stamps, 1925 (Box 114, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 230-589. Organization
    - Tallulah Falls Railway, 1948 (Box 114, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 230-595. Organization
    - Cincinnati, 1926-1929 (Box 114, Folder 67)
    - Cincinnati, 1921-1925 (Box 114, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 230-596. Organization
    - Organization by Tom Walsh, unauthorized organizer, 1924 (Box 114, Folder 69)
  - Sub-Series 230-598. Organization
    - Proposed Ladies Auxiliary, 1922 (Box 114, Folder 70)
  - Sub-Series 230-599. Organization
    - American Carloading Company, 1939 (Box 114, Folder 71)
  - Sub-Series 230-600. Organization
    - Apalachicola Northern Railroad Company, 1939-1941 (Box 114, Folder 72)
  - Sub-Series 230-601. Organization
    - Eastern Public Cattle Market, Montreal, 1940 (Box 114, Folder 73)
  - Sub-Series 230-602. Organization
    - Chesapeake Western Railway, 1940-1941 (Box 114, Folder 74)
  - Sub-Series 230-603. Organization
    - Trona Railway Company, 1940-1952 (Box 114, Folder 75)
  - Sub-Series 230-604. Organization
    - Kansas City Railroad Clearing House Association, 1940-1955 (Box 114, Folder 76)
  - Sub-Series 230-606. Organization
    - California Western Railroad & Navigation Company, 1941 (Box 114, Folder 77)
  - Sub-Series 230-607. Organization
    - City of Princeville Railway, 1941 (Box 114, Folder 78)
  - Sub-Series 230-608. Organization
    - South Georgia, 1940-1955 (Box 114, Folder 79)
  - Sub-Series 230-610. Organization
    - Tennessee Railroad, 1941-1947 (Box 114, Folder 80)
  - Sub-Series 230-611. Organization
    - Seniority Roster, General Representatives to Grand Lodge, 1929 (Box 114, Folder 81)
  - Sub-Series 230-612. Organization
    - Canadian Pacific Airlines, 1947-1949 (Box 114, Folder 82)
  - Sub-Series 230-613. Organization
    - Montour Railroad, 1947-1948 (Box 114, Folder 83)
  - Sub-Series 230-614. Organization
    - Chicago Railways Hotel Ticket Offices, 1947 (Box 114, Folder 84)
  - Sub-Series 230-615. Organization
    - Santa Fe Skyways, 1947-1949 (Box 114, Folder 85)
  - Sub-Series 230-616. Organization
    - National Air Terminal Service Company, Inc., 1947-1951 (Box 114, Folder 86)
  - Sub-Series 230-617. Organization
    - Railway Employees Association of America, 1947 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 230-618. Organization
    - Old Point Comfort Joint Agency, 1946-1947 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 230-622. Organization
    - Pioneer Air Lines, 1947-1949 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 230-623. Organization
    - Empire Air Lines, Idaho, 1947-1949 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 230-626. Organization
    - Midland Railway Company of Manitoba, 1947 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 230-629. Organization
    - Boston & Maine Transportation Company, 1947-1948 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 230-630. Organization
    - Huntington and Broadtop Mountain Railroad, 1947-1948 (Box 115, Folder 7)